<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Terminal Tinkerer</title><link>https://terminaltinkerer.com/</link><description>Recent content on The Terminal Tinkerer</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 10:13:07 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://terminaltinkerer.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About me</title><link>https://terminaltinkerer.com/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 10:13:07 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://terminaltinkerer.com/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>The Terminal Tinkerer&lt;/strong> is a blog site that publishes guides and technical deep dives on cloud infrastructure, container orchestration, and modern software development/delivery practices.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hi, my name is Sid. I&amp;rsquo;m a developer with a passion for learning and writing. Welcome to my blog!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I started my journey as a &lt;em>software developer&lt;/em> in 2018 and have since expanded into &lt;em>software delivery and cloud infrastructure management&lt;/em>. During that time I&amp;rsquo;ve collaborated with customers during application implementation phases and worked with technical teams to solve &lt;em>system integration&lt;/em> challenges. These days I focus on &lt;em>infrastructure management and developer productivity&lt;/em> while managing &lt;em>software deployment on private cloud and on-prem cloud environments&lt;/em>. Wearing multiple hats in a small-to-medium scale business is where I get my fix for solving problems.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Why start a blog?</title><link>https://terminaltinkerer.com/posts/purpose/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 07:59:17 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://terminaltinkerer.com/posts/purpose/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="why-start-a-blog">
 Why start a blog?
 &lt;a class="heading-link" href="#why-start-a-blog">
 &lt;i class="fa-solid fa-link" aria-hidden="true" title="Link to heading">&lt;/i>
 &lt;span class="sr-only">Link to heading&lt;/span>
 &lt;/a>
&lt;/h1>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>To capture my mistakes and wins as I tinker with tech&lt;/li>
&lt;li>To share ideas and create guides for others who may stumble along the same path&lt;/li>
&lt;li>To learn from your feedback&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>I enjoy working on problems that challenge me, but once I solve them, I quickly move on to the next challenge. Over time, I forget some of the interesting things I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on in the past. This blog will serve as a personal archive. Encouraging me to review my notes and reflect on the lessons I&amp;rsquo;ve learned over the years and share them with you.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>